声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon  憨妹 闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
Charlie?
和我一块儿去散步怎样?
How about you and I go for a walk?
不
No.
不  不去  Locke  今天我哪儿都不想去
No thanks, Locke.I'm gonna stay in today.
来吧
Come on.
新鲜空气对你有好处
Fresh air will do you good.
我的照片要比这好看多了
I take better pictures than that.
而且  如果你想放皮夹里的话 这张显然太小了
Smaller too, if you want something for your wallet.
我过来取些东西  这...
I just came by for a few things and this was...
这照片和我的东西放一块了
This was with my stuff.
就是说  你不会留下了?
So you're not staying?
你可以说我脱离集体
Call me a broken record,
但山洞是一个天然的屏障
but caves are natural shelter.
呆在那儿比呆在海边要安全多了
And a hell of a lot safer than living on the beach.
你在生我的气
You're mad at me.
没有  Kate  我...
No.Kate, I'm...
我只是搞不懂你为什么不和我...我们一块儿过去
I just don't understand why you won't come with me...us.
过去住的话  也就一英里的路
It's maybe a mile up there, if that.
我们出事已有8天了  Jack
We crashed eight days ago, Jack.
-我不是要在这儿安家  -我也想离开这岛
-I'm not setting up house here.  -I want off this island, too,
但我们都清楚 短期内是不可能离开的
but we both know that's not gonna happen anytime soon.
Sayid有个计划
Sayid has a plan.
我知道 寻找求救码的信号发源处  是吧
Yeah, to find the source of the distress code. I know.
那信号来自岛屿的某个地方
That signal's coming from somewhere on the island.
那信号已重复循环了16年了  Kate
The signal has been running on a loop for 16 years, Kate.
但那个发求救信号的女子 并没有被解救
And the woman that left it, she wasn't rescued.
你凭什么认为一定 会有人来救我们?
What makes you think it's gonna be any different for us?
我相信
I believe it.
我很想自己能分享你的信仰
I wish I shared your faith.
我不介意和她分享一些东西
I wouldn't mind sharing a few things with her myself.
你想要什么  Sawyer?
What do you want, Sawyer?
听说医生要来这儿占位置
Heard the doc here is vacating the premises.
我想我最好抢在别人前面 把这地方占了
Thought I best lay claimsv to my new digs before somebody else did.
我会把这儿弄的舒舒服服的
I can fix this place up real good.
我甚至发现有人要和我一块儿分享
I might even find somebody to share it with me.
以后再聊吧
I'll talk to you later.
是你吗?
Is that you?
保佑我  神父  因为我的过失
Bless me, father, for I have sinned.
距上一次忏悔有1个礼拜了
It's been a week since my last confession.
继续  我的孩子
Go ahead, my son.
昨晚  我...
Last night I had...
我和一个不相识的女子发生了关系
physical relations with a girl I didn't even know.
我明白  还有呢?
I see. Anything else?
这过后我又...
Yeah. Uh, right after that, I had...
我又和另一女子发生了关系
relations with another girl.
完事以后  我又看她们俩...
Then straight after that, I watched while they had...
看她们发生那种关系
relations with each other.
你知道  这是我的乐队  神父..."驱轴乐队"
You see, it's my band, father...Driveshaft.
当时我们在曼彻斯特表演
We've been playing the clubs in Manchester, and, uh...
大家都玩得很兴奋
we've been getting some heat,
随后  你知道
a following, you know, and...
那些女子...
the girls...
她们来到我们的地方  你知道 真的是很诱惑人
there's some real temptations that come with the territory,
如果你知道我在说什么的话
if you know what I mean.
生活中我们会碰到很多的诱惑
Well, we all have our temptations,
但屈服于诱惑 那只是你的选择
but giving into them --that's your choice.
我们活在这世上
As we live our lives,
生活就是要你作出选择  难道不是吗?
it's really nothing but a series of choices, isn't it?
我已经作好了我的选择
Well, then I've made my choice.
我要离开乐队
I have to quit the band.
谦恭将降临这个地球
And the meek shall inherit the earth.
Liam  你在干什么?  这是教堂  把腿放下来
Liam. What are you doing? This is a church. Get your boots off.
不要急  唱诗班的小家伙
Relax, choirboy.
我给你带来了另人振奋的好消息
I bring good tidings of great joy.
我们刚刚签约了
We've just been signed.
一个出唱片的合同
A recording contract.
你会成为摇滚之神的
You're gonna be a rock god.
干的好  Charlie
Nice work, Charlie.
你真是个好诱饵
You make excellent bait.
很高兴我帮得上忙
I'm glad I could oblige.
现在把毒品还我
Now give me my bloody drugs.
你听到我说的话了么?
Did you hear what I said?
我要你把毒品还我
I want my drugs back.
我需要毒品!
I need them!
但是是你自己给我的
Yet you gave them to me.
我真他妈后悔给了你!
And I bloody well regret it!
我病了  老兄!
I'm sick, man!
你看不出来吗?!
Can't you see that?
你比你想象的要坚强得多  Charlie
I think you're a lot stronger than you know, Charlie.
这我会证明给你看
And I'm gonna prove it to you.
我允许你三次向我要毒品
I'll let you ask me for your drugs three times.
第三次的时候  我会把毒品给你
The third time, I'm gonna give them to you.
现在明白了吧  这算是第一次
Now, just so we're clear, this is one.
为什么?为什么?你为什么要这么做?
Why? Why? Why are you doing this?
折磨我?
To torture me?
你还是放弃吧  尽快把毒品给我
ust get rid of them and have done with it.
如果我这么做了 那你连个选择都没有了  Charlie
If I did that, you wouldn't have a choice, Charlie.
而且比起本能 作出选择或决定
And having choices, making decisions based on more than instinct
是唯一能够把你和它区别开来的
is the only thing that separates you from him.
三根天线
Three antennae.
作为三角形的三个点
Three points of a triangle.
一根插在海边
One here on the beach.
另一根  Kate将把它插在 丛林内部大约2公里处
Another Kate will position in the jungle roughly 2 kilometers in.
第三根  我会带到高地去--就那儿
And the third, I'll take to high ground --up there.
如果那法国信号
If the french transmission
是来自这三角范围的某个地方
is coming from somewhere within our triangulation,
我就能定位这个信号发射地
I'll be able to locate the source.
但还是有两个难点
But there are two complications.
那是肯定的
Of course there are.
我安置在天线内的电量不多
The power cells I crafted onto the antennas are dry.
我也不知道能维持多久
There's no telling how long they'll last.
一分钟  或许要多  或许要少
A minute, maybe more, maybe less.
所以只有大家都就位了 才能启动天线装置!
So we have to wait until we're in position before we switch them on?
我们怎么知道对方都已经就位了?
How are we gonna be able to tell that we're actually in the right position?
我们相互之间没办法联系
We have no way to communicate with each other.
炮筒?
Bottle rockets?
感谢上帝允许烟火的走私
Thank god for fireworks smugglers.
听着 当我就位以后  我会发射炮筒
Now, when I'm in position, I'll fire off my rocket.
你俩看见以后  同时发射你们的
When you two see it, you fire yours.
最后一个炮筒一升天
As soon as the last one has gone up,
我们就迅速启动天线装置
we'll all switch on our antennas.
好的  但你说有两个难处
Okay, but you said that there are two complications.
接收机是没电的
The battery in the transceiver is dead.
没有接收机  这一切都将是白忙活
Without the transceiver, all of this is for nothing.
笔记本中的有些部件可能会有用
Something from a laptop computer would probably work,
但我找不到
but I've not been able to find anything.
我想我知道去哪儿找
I think I might know where to look.
自从坠机后  你就像美洲大鼠 一样会藏东西
You've been hoarding like a pack rat since the crash,
却连一台笔记本都没有?
and you don't have a single laptop?
我们都是易怒的
We are testy.
还在因分手烦恼?
Still upset about your little breakup?
你和Jacko?
You and Jacko?
一定很累
Must be exhausting.
你说什么?
What's that?
像寄生虫一样活着
Living like a parasite.
只入不出
Always taking, never giving.
你要我去干活  是吧?
Boy, you've got me pegged, don't you?
我明白了
I get it now.
你不想离开这个岛 是因为回去也没什么好留恋的
You don't want off this island because there's nothing for you to go back for.
没有你思念的人
Nobody you miss.
也没人思念你
And no one misses you.
你是不是同情我了?
Oh, are you feeling sorry for me?
我没同情你
I don't feel sorry for you.
我可怜你
I pity you.
你所要做的就是说声"请"
All you had to do was say "please."
伙计  这里面什么东西  煤块吗?
Dude, what's in these things, cinder blocks?
我把我认为会用到的东西都带来了 以备不时之需
I packed everything I thought might be useful here without leaving the others shorthanded.
要帮忙吗?
Hey, do you guys need a hand?
以前在乐队有专门托运人员之前 都是我们自己拉装备的
I used to lug the band's equipment before we had roadies, way back in the day.
-让我... -不  Charlie  拉链是...
-Here, let me ---No, Charlie, the zipper's...
抱歉  我想帮忙的
Sorry. I was just trying to help.
我知道  没关系
I know. It's okay.
嘿  帮我把剩下的包裹搬来好吗?
Hey, want to help me grab the rest of those bags?
我行的吗?
Could I?
...有点头疼
... have a headache.
镇定安眠药
Diazepam.
那是治疗焦虑的
It's for anxiety.
-我在找阿斯匹林  -对头疼来说  这种药效很强
-I was looking for aspirin.  -Pretty strong stuff for a headache.
是的
Yeah, right.
你没事吧?你看起来有点...
Hey, you okay? You're looking a little...
我  不  我没事 就是有点头疼
I...no, it's nothing. It's just a headache.
Charlie  随它去吧 去取些水 你可能是脱水了
Charlie, leave it. Go get some water. Maybe you're dehydrated.
Charlie  我来就行了
Charlie, I got it.
你先照顾好自己
Go take care of yourself, man.
我暂时不需要你的帮忙
I don't need youright now.
拜托  Charlie  没有你我们做不成
Come on, Charlie boy, we can't do this without you.
你才是他妈的"驱轴灵魂"
You are bloody Driveshaft.
注意语言
Watch the language.
现在是我们出风头的大好时机
This is our shot at the big time.
什么?  难道你不想成名?
What? You don't want to be famous?
我不是为了那个  我只关心我的音乐
It's not about all that. I only care about the music.
是的  你的音乐  是你的歌让我们签的约
Yeah, your music. Your songs that got us signed.
我只是一个有着漂亮脸蛋 唱着你的歌的小丑
I'm just a clown with a pretty face that sings them.
你想把机会让给别人?
And you want to take away my chance to be somebody?
Liam  这不是你的缘故
Liam, it's not about you.
这是...
It's...
我爱这只乐队
I love the band.
但这不是真正的我
It's not who I am.
有时  我总感觉有点迷失
Sometimes I just get lost in it.
不会再那样了  因为我会一如既往的照顾你
Won't happen, 'cause I'll be there looking out for you.
我们大家都相互照顾 那不是兄弟间应该做的事吗?
We'll look outfor each other...what brothers do, right?
对吧?
Right?
等! 等! 等! 等...
Wait, wait! Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
答应我一件事
Just promise me one thing.
如果事情变得太过疯狂
If things get too crazy,
不管怎样
no matter what,
如果我说我们就此结束
if I say we're done,
我们立马走人
we walk away.
We walk away.
Liam  你得承诺
Liam, promise.
我们立马走人
We walk away.
小兄弟  你是摇滚之神
You're the rock god, baby brother.
坏家伙!
Aah! Wanker!
你应该让医生检查一下你的手腕
没事  会好的
看你怎么穿的?
太不雅观了
多穿点
太热了
伙计  这是你的?
Hey, dude, this yours?
是的
Oh, yeah.
你一定有疑问  因为我是驱轴乐队的贝斯手
Probably wondering because I play bass in Driveshaft.
我还写了很多的曲子
I wrote a bunch of tunes on that.
听着  伙计  Jack要你把吉他放在其它地方
Listen, man, Jack just wants you to find another placefor it.
他有东西要搬来  马上就到了
He's moving supplies and says it's in the way.
你知道  有多少人崇拜我吗!
You know, a lot of people look up to me.
他们尊重我
They respect me.
而你...却把我当成他妈的小孩子
And you...you just treat me like I'm some bloody child,
好像我是个无用的笑话
like I'm some useless joke.
你在说什么呀?
What are you talking about?
"Charlie做不好这个"
"Charlie's not good enough to do this,"
"Charlie挡着路了"
"Charlie's just in the way."
坐下  让我看看你
Sit down. Let me take a look at you.
你要照顾我是吧?
Oh, you're gonna look out for me, yeah?
我们是相互照顾的  事情就是这样
We'll look out for each other. That's how it is.
Charlie  冷静  好吗? 你失控了
Charlie, just calm down, all right? You're not yourself right now.
你不了解我  我是他妈的摇滚之神!
You don't know me. I'm a bloody rock god!
不
Oh, no.
Charlie  Jack在哪?
Charlie, where's Jack?
Jack在哪?
Where's Jack?
Jack! Jack  能听到我说话吗?!
Jack! Jack, can you hear me?!
我们刚在聊天  石头就这么下来了 一切都太突然了
We were just talking, and it came down on us. It all happened so fast.
我们需要帮助
Dude, we gotta get help.
Charlie  你去海边叫些人手过来!
Charlie, go down to the beach and get help!
好  我这就去
Okay, I'm on it.
别忘了告诉Kate!
And make sure you tell Kate!
我们要怎么做...
What we're doing...
追踪一些虚幻的求救信号
chasing some phantom distress signal...
如果行了  那真是太神奇了
what are the odds of this working?
和我们能够在 飞机失事中存活一样神奇
No worse than the odds of our surviving that plane crash.
一直以来都有人在飞机失事中存活的
People survive plane crashes all the time
但这次不一样
Not like this one.
在我们还在空中的时候 尾舱就已经折断了
The tail section broke off when we were still in the air.
我们这部分舱像翻跟斗一样 跌进了丛林里
Our section cartwheeled through the jungle,
除了一些刮伤  我们成功的活了下来
and yet we escaped with nothing but a few scrapes.
这又如何解释?
How do you explain that?
中大运了
Blind dumb luck.
没人会这么幸运的
No one's that lucky.
本来我们已经死了
We shouldn't have survived.
抱歉  Sayid
Sorry, Sayid,
但事情就这么发生了
but some things just happen...
没有规律  也没有原因
no rhyme, no reason.
我们需要帮忙!
Hey! We need help!
-怎么了?  -是Jack  他出事了
-What's wrong, man?  -It's Jack. He's trapped.
什么?
What?
山洞倒塌了 我们甚至不知道他是否还活着
A cave collapsed. We don't even know if he's alive.
-快  我们得走了  -Scott?
-Come on, we got to go.  -Hey, uh, Scott?
-我是Steve  -我是Scott
-I'm Steve.  -I'm Scott.
事情很紧急  叫些人走吧..
We got an emergency. Grab a couple guys and let's go.
我们得走了
We got to go now.
快  我们得走了
Hey, come on. Let's go.
Shannon  你得准备好做一件 很重要的事  好吗?
Shannon, you have to be ready to do something really important, okay?
5:00点
5:00 sharp.
你得准备好启动那个天线装置
You need to be ready to turn that antenna on over there.
底部有个开关
There's a switch at the base.
为什么?
Why?
因为Kate和Sayid正在三角定位 那个求救信号
Because Kate and Sayid are triangulating the french signal.
但天线的电力很弱
But the antenna's power is really weak,
所以你得等着  直到他们把炮筒发射上天
so you have to wait until they fire their bottle rockets.
然后你也点燃炮筒
Then you fire this one,
接着就启动天线装置  明白了吗?
then you turn on the antenna. Got it?
开关在哪?
Switch is where now?
你听到我说什么了吗  你到底是能还是不能?
Did you hear a word I said? Can you or can't you do it?
-当然我能  -好  好的
-Yeah, I can.  -Okay. Okay.
等等  Kate
Wait. Kate.
我们得把Jack这事告诉Kate
Hey, we have to tell Kate about Jack!
抱歉  爱跑腿的  你错过了
Sorry, sport. Just missed her.
她和"穆罕默德"大约10分钟前去树林了
Her and Muhammed headed into the woods about 10 minutes ago.
哪边走的?
Which way?
不要焦虑了 朋友  我知道他们往哪边走的
Don't sweat it, amigo. I know which way they went.
-是的  但...  -我会告诉她的
-Yeah, but...  -I'll tell her.
你尽管做...随便你做什么...
You just keep doing...whatever it is you do around here.
好
All right.
好  好的
All right, all right.
感谢你出来
Hey, mate. Thanks for coming out.
Liam!
你怎么回事?
What the hell was that?
又一场精彩的表演 你光彩四射
Another kick-ass show. You were bloody brilliant.
那句合唱词"you all,everybody."应该是我领的
I sing the chorus to "you all, everybody."
是的抱歉
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
感觉那时我特兴奋 而且观众都想这样
It's like I got caught up in the moment, like the crowd wanted it.
是我知道 但如果我先开始  你随后...
Yeah, I know, but if I start, and then you come in after...
她可以! 让她进来!
She's cool! Let her in!
我发誓这不会再发生了
Won't happen again. I promise.
Allo  亲爱的
Allo, lovely.
放松点儿  小兄弟
Chill, baby brother.
等等!等等  Jack在里面
Hey! Hey, wait! Wait, Jack's in there.
移动之前先让我检查一下 万一这不稳...
Letme check it out before youstart moving things around. If it's unstable...
-哦  你怎么知道...  -8年的建筑工作
-Well, how do you know...  -Eight yearsof construction work.
Walt  退后  不要靠近岩石  行不?
Walt, get back, man. I don't want younear the rocks, okay?
还有看好你的狗
And take the dog with you.
你们应该去找Locke先生
You guys should get mr. Locke.
Locke在丛林里抓掠物 谁知道他现在在哪?
Locke's out in the jungle killing stuff. Who knows where he is?
好  听着  这地方十分不稳
All right, look, this area here is load-bearing.
我们得在一个稳固的 没有危险的墙壁处挖
We got to dig where there's no danger of the wall buckling in on itself.
好  就这儿  我们在这儿挖 这儿的墙不会塌下来
All right, here. We dig in here so the wall doesn't collapse.
每次四个人  用手挖 除非能找到铲子
Four at a time, by hand till we can find some kind of shovel.
我们轮流挖  慢慢挖
We take shifts and go slow.
没有挖的人就清理挖出来的岩石
Whoever isn't digging should be clearing the rocks that we pull out
还有给干活的人递水  行吗?
and bringing water to who is working, okay?
行动  来吧
Let's move. Come on.
你来这儿干什么?
What the hell are you doing here?
我只是来告诉你一些事
I just came to tell you you were right about me.
你凭什么认为 我会对你要告诉我的事感兴趣?
What makes you think I'm interested in anything you have to say?
我只是来告诉你  你说得很对
I just came to tell you you were right about me.
除了自己  我不会帮助别人
That I don't help anyone but myself.
我来了  准备投入工作
Well, here I am, ready to pitch in.
你来这儿帮忙?
You're here to help?
你的表现让我惊讶  这让我很不舒服
You act any more surprised, I'm gonna get offended.
出事了?Charlie?
Something wrong, Charlie?
是的
Yeah.
Jack
他
He's, uh...
山洞发生了意外
there's been an accident at the caves.
Jack被困在洞里了
Jack's trapped in a cave-in.
有人在想法子弄他出来吗?
Is anyone trying to get him out?
有  那儿有一大堆人
Yeah, there's a bunch of people there now.
你为什么不和他们呆在一块儿?
And why aren't you with them?
你来不只是想告诉我Jack的事  是吧?
You didn't come here to tell me about Jack, did you?
我想要回我的东西  Locke
I want my stash, Locke.
我受不了了
I can't stand feeling like this.
过来  我给你看样东西
Come here. I'm gonna show you something.
你认为茧里面是什么东西  Charlie?
What do you suppose is in that cocoon, Charlie?
我不知道  蝴蝶吗?
I don't know, a butterfly, I guess.
不是  比蝴蝶漂亮多了 这是一个蛾的茧
No, it's much more beautiful than that. That's a moth cocoon.
很讽刺是吧!蝴蝶很引人注目  但蛾 --它们吐丝
It's ironic. Butterflies get all the attention, but moths --they spin silk.
它们更快更强壮
They're stronger, they're faster.
-太奇妙了  但...  -你看到这小洞了?
-That's wonderful, but...  -You see this little hole?
这蛾快破茧了
This moth's just about to emerge.
它现在在里面挣扎着
It's in there right now, struggling.
慢慢地挖出一条道 穿破厚厚的保护层
It'sdigging its way through the thick hide of the cocoon.
现在  我可以帮它
Now,I could help it
用这把刀子
take my knife,
轻轻的划出一道口子  蛾就自由了
gently widen the opening, and the moth would be free.
但它太弱了  以致于根本活不下来
But it would be too weak to survive.
挣扎是变得强大的自然方法
Struggle is nature's way of strengthening.
现在  这是你第二次向我要回毒品
Now, this is the second time you've asked me for your drugs back.
再问我要一次  这就是你的了
Ask me again, and it's yours.
通了!有个洞了!
We're through! We got a hole!
Jack! Jack!  能听到我说话吗?  Jack?
Jack! Jack, can you hear me, Jack?
拜托  伙计  回答我呀
Come on, dude, answer me
我听到他了!他还活着!
I hear him! He's alive!
Jack老兄  你没事吧?
Jack, bro, you okay?
我被夹住了  动不了了
I'm pinned. I can't move.
我移动不了!
I can't move!
我们怎么办?
What do we do?
怎么把他弄出来?
How do we get him out?
Charlie和我在一起的!
Charlie was with me!
-他没事  他出来了  -听着  Jack?
-He's okay. He made it out.  -Hey, listen, Jack?
我们会把你弄出来的
We're gonna get you outta there, okay?
第二根天线就安置在这吧
We'll place the second antenna here.
想帮忙?
You want to help?
把这根天线安装在那边的树上 越高越好
Attach this antenna up in that tree as high up as you can.
哦  谢了 头
Golly, thanks, boss.
5:00点
5:00.
看着我的信号灯 然后就轮到你发射
Watch for my flare. Then it's your turn.
我不信任他
I don't trust him.
谁会呢?
Who does?
我不放心你和他在一起
I don't trust him with you.
我会处理好他的
I can handle him.
我们不能把洞弄得再大了 太危险了
Okay, we can't safely make that tunnel any bigger,
但Jack还是出不来
but since Jack can't get out,
我们当中必须有人进去 帮他移开乱石
one of us is gonna have to go in and unpin him.
什么  爬进去吗?
What, crawl through that?
我想他的意思是小点个子的
I think he means someone smaller.
-伙计  我们听不懂中国话  -是韩语  老兄
-Dude, we don't understand chinese.  -Korean, man.
他们是韩国人
They're korean.
-我来吧  -Charlie?
-I'll do it.  -Charlie?
不  听着  你还没恢复过来 或许我可以爬进去
No, man, look, you're still too shook up. I might be able to squeeze
等等  如果发生什么事 谁来照顾你的孩子?
Wait. Who's gonna take care of your son if something happens?
她有丈夫 而他有个妹妹
She's got a husband. He's got a sister.
这儿只有我是单身的
I'm alone here.
找不出其他人了
No one on the island.
我来做吧
Let me do this.
还不到5:00点 好象你是最后一次看手表似的
Still ain't 5:00, just like the last time you checked your watch.
我只是不想错过Sayid的信号
I just don't want to miss Sayid's signal.
记住  我来点火  你启动天线装置
Remember, I'll fire the flare. You set off the antenna.
真该感谢上帝 有你这么个老提醒我的家伙
I just thank the good lord I got you here to keep reminding me.
这活并不好干 但总得有人来做
It's a dirty job, but somebody's gotta do it.
那家伙哪儿吸引你了?
So what is it about that guy?
Jack?
他什么地方让你...
What is it about him that makes you all...
抵不住腰部的诱惑?
weak in the loins?
你想做猪  还是天生就这样?
You try to be a pig, or it just come naturally?
他是个医生  对吧?
So he's a doctor, right?
是的  女士喜欢医生
Yeah, ladies dig the doctors.
给我一卷绷带
Hell, give me a couple of band-aids,
一瓶过氧化氢 我也能做个领导者
a bottle of peroxide, I could run this island, too.
你在把你和Jack作比较?
You're actually comparing yourself to Jack?
我们间并没有很大的区别  宝贝
Difference between us ain't that big, sweetheart.
我敢说  要是他能够再多活几周的话
I guarantee you if he had survived a few more weeks on this island,
你就会明白的
you'd have figured that out.
你刚说什么?
What did you just say?
我这蠢蛋 我说了吗?
Ah,damn. Didn't I tell you?
山谷传来声音说圣人Jack被埋进洞里了
Word from the valley is St. Jack got himself buried in a cave-in.
往好的方面想 现在你总算有人可同情了
Look at the bright side. Now you have someone else to pity.
听着  伙计  慢慢爬  好吗?
Listen, man, go slow, all right?
不要推身边的石块
Try not to nudge any of the rocks around you.
还有呢?
Anything else?
是的
Yeah.
好运
Good luck.
小心点  老兄
Be safe, man.
祝你好运  Charlie
Good luck, Charlie.
好吧  谢谢  朋友们
All right. Thanks, guys.
晕啊
Bloody hell.
小兄弟  随你挑哪个妞  坐吧
Hey, baby brother, grab a bird and sit down.
出去
Get out.
你也是  出去
You too, get out.
快  现在!!
Come on, now.
5分种后回来
Come back in five minutes.
声道检测
Sound check.
你误了声道检测
You missed sound check.
你连排练都没来
You don't show up for rehearsal.
一小时后就要表演了
We've got a show in an hour.
表演  我喜欢表演
Ooh, show. I like shows.
是的
Ah, yeah.
好
All right.
够了
That's it.
今晚过后  剩下的巡回演出全部取消
After tonight, we cancel the rest of the tour.
大家走人
And walk away.
你想就此了事?
Are you off your end?
我们说好当事情变得..... 我们就走人
We're walking away like we said we would if things got
走人?去哪?
Walk away and go where?
Liam  这些垃圾会害了你的!
Liam, you're killing yourself with this junk!
-你在毁了整个"驱轴乐队" -我就是"驱轴乐队"!
-You're destroying Driveshaft!-I am Driveshaft!
甚至没人知道贝斯手是谁!
Nobody even knows who the sodding bass player is!
行了  Charlie
This is it, Charlie.
事情都这样了
End of the rainbow.
你真认为你能走人?
Do you really think you can walk away?
知道不  恩?
Then what, eh?
面对吧  看看这个乐队  你在乐队有个屁用啊?
Face it, if you're notin this band, what the bloody hell use are you?
Liam
滚开!
Piss off!
Charlie?!
Charlie  快爬!
Charlie, move!
Charlie!
我  ...
I'm, uh...
我是来救你的
I'm here to rescue you.
-我们再试一次  -我们不能就这么走了...
-I say we try again.  -We can't just leave
如果我们走了  他们会闷死在里面的
If we don't move, they're gonna run out of air.
嘿  不要再说了!再仔细想想
would you stop talking? I'm trying to think!
他在哪儿?他在哪儿?!
Where is he? Where is he?!
Kate
他在哪儿?Jack在哪儿?
Where is he? Where's Jack?
他在里面
He's in there.
他还活着吗?
Does anyone know if he's alive?
-他还活着吗?!  -我们不知道
-Is he alive?!  -We don't know.
我们挖了一条道  Charlie爬进去了
Charlie went in there through a tunnel that we dug,
但又塌了
but it collapsed.
为什么不挖了?
Why 1is nobody digging?
好  1  2... 3!
Okay, 1, 2... 3!
对不起  Jack  对不起
Sorry, Jack. Sorry.
你还行吗?
You all right?
我肩膀脱臼了
My shoulder is dislocated.
你得帮我把它弄回去
You're gonna have to pop it back in.
-不  我做不到  -我需要你的帮忙  伙计
-No, I can't.  -I need your help on this, man.
-我真做不到  Jack  -行的  你做的到的
-I can't do it, Jack.  -Yes, you can.
你能做到的
Yes, you can.
好吧
Okay.
那我...那我该怎么做?
What do I...what do I do?
抓住我的手
Take my hand.
等等  好  好  等
Just a sec. Okay. Okay, wait.
好  好了
Okay. Okay.
现在  我一说拉 你就尽最大的力气拉
Now, when I tell you to, pull as hard as you possibly can.
Jack  我不知道我是否能...我不知道...
Jack, I don't know if I can...I don't...
你能够做到的  Charlie
You can do this, Charlie.
好  好  好...
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
拉
Now.
Charlie
你来干吗了?
What you doing here?
什么  这么长时间 小子就不能来拜访大兄弟了?
What, a bloke can't pay his big brother a visit once in a while?
当然可以  真蠢 干吗不先打个电话?
Of course he can. Why didn't you call, you lunatic?
你在悉尼做什么呢?
What are you doing in Sydney?
都安排妥当了  Liam
It's all lined up, Liam.
跟随一个叫"Meat Coat"的乐队 巡回演出8周
Eight weeks on tour opening for some band called Meat Coat.
第一场演唱会在洛山矶举办
First gig's in Los Angeles.
洛山矶啊  Liam
L.A., Liam.
这是再次给自己 打造品牌的好机会啊
This is a chance to get back on a label.
一个真正的机会
A real one.
是我们复出的时候了
This is our comeback.
Charlie  我不想复出了
Charlie, I don't want to come back.
好  呃  事情其实是这样
Yeah, right. Well, here's the thing.
没有你  他们就不要"驱轴乐队"
They won't book Driveshaft without you.
所以我请你...
So I'm asking...
以一个兄弟的身份...
as a brother...
就如你以前请我一样
the way you asked me.
我错过Megan生日的那晚 你和我在一起
You were with me the night I missed Megan's birth.
你是一块我想在Drenden开演唱会的绊脚石
You were the one I was stumbling around Dresden with trying to find a sodding fix.
-伙计  你还在用  是不是?  -不要转换话题
-Ah, man, you're still using, aren't you?  -Oh, don't change the subject.
那就是你不回我电话的原因
That's why you haven't been returning my calls.
-这巡回演出  你到底去还是不去?  -你说过你会戒掉的
-You gonna go on tour with us or not?  -You said you'd get help, man.
-你的号码  我找不到了  -看来你还是有毒隐!
-I lost your sodding number.  -You're still a junkie!
是你把我弄成这样的!
Well, you did this to me!
还说是为了音乐!
It was about the music!
音乐  Liam
Music, Liam.
你把它从我身上带走了
You took that away from me.
听着  你和我们一块儿住几周吧!
Listen, why don't you stay with us for a few weeks?
Karen和我会想办法帮你的
Karen and me, we can get you help.
悉尼还是有很多好节目的
Sydney's got some really good programs.
算了吧
Forget it.
不要走
Don't go.
-感谢你的帮忙  兄弟  -留下吧  求你了
-Thanks for your help, brother.  -Stay, please.
我要照顾好你的!
I'm just looking out for you!
你从来没照顾过我!
You never looked out for me!
我还有个计划
I have a plane to catch.
这样已经多久了  Charlie?
How long has it been, Charlie?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're going on about.
距离上一次吸毒已经多久了?
How long since your last fix?
差不多有1天半了
Almost a day and a half.
没毒品吸  感觉怎样?
How's the withdrawal treating you?
有幻觉?
Any hallucinations?
除了和你一小时前 在丛林里的谈话
Apart from the conversation I had with you about an hour ago in the jungle?
应该说没有
No, not really.
你干吗不说出来?
Why didn't you say anything?
我可以帮你度过这个难关的
I could have helped you through this.
是的  你一定认为我是个没用的 彻头彻尾的隐君子
Yeah. You thinking I'm useless and a junkie to boot.
没用?
Useless?
你才不会没用
You're not useless.
爬进来救我需要多么大的勇气
That took a lot of guts getting in here and trying to rescue me.
我不会忘记的
I won't forget that.
我们的余生吗?
For the rest of our lives?
以我们呼吸氧气的速度
At the rate we're using our oxygen in here,
维持不了多久了
that won't be too long.
这地方...
This place...
让我想到忏悔
it reminds me of confession.
在这个狭小紧闭的空间
This little claustrophobic booth.
我还不知道你是个有宗教信仰的人
I wouldn't have taken you for a religious man.
我过去是
I used to be.
想听我祷告吗?
Hey, you want to hear my confession?
或许得花点时间
It might take a while.
我也不是什么高徒
Hey, I'm no saint, either.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
有蛾
There's a moth.
有什么?
A what?
就在你后面  看  看
Right behind you. Look, look.
这儿有哦!!
There's a bloody moth in here.
看
Look.
Charlie  你干什么?
Charlie, what are you doing?
Kate  你休息一下吧
Hey, Kate, you need to take a break.
我没事儿
I'm fine.
挖的人够了
We got enough people to dig.
你要是保持这样的节奏挖 自己会先垮的
You keep going at this pace, you're gonna kill yourself.
有光
There's light.
什么?
What?
我看见光了!
I can see light!
是医生!
Hey, it's the doctor!
轻点儿!
Oh! Ow! Easy!
我的肩
My shoulder.
小心
Careful.
你们怎么出来的?
How'd you get out?
Charlie  是Charlie想的办法出来的
Charlie. Charlie found a way out.
老兄  你太棒了!
Dude, you rock!
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
没事吧?干得漂亮
You okay? Good job.
放松一下  放松  放松...
Easy, easy, easy.
-干得好  你成功了  伙计  -谢谢  谢谢
-Nice work. You did it, man.  -Thanks. Thank you.
好了  各位  轮到你们了
All right, everyone, now it's your turn.
有段时间我们住在Malibu 但那儿的家伙真是白痴...
We're in Malibu part of the year, but the guys there are such idiots...
糟了!
Damn it!
糟了  糟了  糟了....
Damn it, damn it, damn it.
快  Kate  快
Come on, Kate. Come on.
再来一个  再来一个  加油  Kate  加油
One more. One more. Come on, Kate. Come on.
好的  好的
Yes. Yes.
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
好的!
Yes!
你在哪?你在哪儿?
Where are you? Where are you?
伙计  你没事吧? 你看起来有点....
Dude, you feeling okay? You look a little...
流感  他得了流感
Flu. He's got the flu.
哦  老兄  难为你了
Oh, man, that's rough.
经历了这一切 放松点儿  老兄
After all you've been through. Take it easy, man.
我想我得去活动一下筋骨
I think I'm gonna stretch my legs.
这地方很酷  我们能住这儿吗?
This place is cool. Can we live here?
给你做了点东西
Made you something.
我的第一条绷带
Ah, my very first sling.
感觉怎样?
How's that?
很好
Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么这些就是你所谓的安全的洞
So these are the safe caves you've been going on about.
这次实在侥幸
This was a fluke.
Michael检查过剩余的洞了 确定没问题
Michael checked out the integrity of the rest of the caves, gave them an okay.
所以你又要回海边去了  恩?
So you're headed back to the beach, huh?
Sayid应该已经回来了 如果计划揍效的话...
Sayid should be back there by now, and if his plan worked...
我们距离开这个岛又近了一步
Then we're one step closer to getting off this island.
谢谢你的"绷带"  Kate
Thanks for the sling, Kate.
不客气
You're welcome.
把它们给我
Give them to me.
这是第三次
This is the third time.
-你确定你真想要...  -我已经作出了决定
-Are you sure you really want...  -I've made my choice.
我替你感到骄傲  Charlie
I'm proud of you, Charlie.
我一直深信你能做到的
I always knew you could do it.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====